Inventory of the Parents' Information Collection, 1972 - 2008
Parents' Information Collection, 1972 - 2008
Special Collections & Archives, Wesleyan University
Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)
1000-126
1.0
2
The Parents' Information Collections includes handbooks and other information sent to parents of incoming and transfer students at Wesleyan University.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisitions Information
Collected by the Wesleyan University Archives.
Collection Overview
The Parents' Information Collections includes handbooks and other information sent to parents of incoming and transfer students at Wesleyan University.
Online Catalog Headings
These and related materials may be found under the following headings in online catalogs.
Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--Students.; Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)
Detailed Description of the Collection
  - Handbook for Wesleyan Parents, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Handbook for Wesleyan Parents, 1973-1974
  - Handbook for Wesleyan Parents, 1974-1975
  - Handbook for Wesleyan Parents, 1975-1976 (Folder 2)
  - Handbook for Wesleyan Parents, 1976-1977
  - Handbook for Wesleyan Parents, 1977-1978
  - Handbook for Wesleyan Parents, 1978-1979
  - Handbook for Wesleyan Parents, 1979-1980
  - Handbook for Wesleyan Parents, 1980-1981 (Folder 3)
  - Handbook for Wesleyan Parents, 1981-1982
  - Handbook for Wesleyan Parents, 1982-1983
  - Handbook for Wesleyan Parents, 1983-1984
  - Handbook for Wesleyan Parents, 1984-1985
  - Handbook for Wesleyan Parents, 1985-1986 (Folder 4)
  - Handbook for Wesleyan Parents, 1986-1987
  - Handbook for Wesleyan Parents, 1987-1988
  - Handbook for Wesleyan Parents, 1988-1989
  - Handbook for Wesleyan Parents, 1989-1990
  - Handbook for Wesleyan Parents, 1990-1991 (Folder 5)
  - Handbook for Wesleyan Parents, 1991-1992
  - Handbook for Wesleyan Parents, 1992-1993
  - Handbook for Wesleyan Parents, 1993-1994
  - Handbook for Wesleyan Parents, 1994-1995
  - Handbook for Wesleyan Parents, 1995-1996 (Folder 6)
  - Handbook for Wesleyan Parents, 1996-1997
  - Wesleyan University Handbook for Parents, 1997-1998
  - Wesleyan University Handbook for Parents, 1998-1999
  - Wesleyan University Handbook for Parents, 1999-2000
  - Wesleyan University Handbook for Parents, 2000-2001 (Folder 7)
  - Wesleyan University Handbook for Parents, 2001-2002
  - Wesleyan University Handbook for Parents, 2003-2004
  - Summer mailing to parents, 2005-2006 (Folder 8)
    Note: Includes the Handbook for Parents and other information regarding upcoming Wesleyan events and the Middletown area.
  - Summer mailing to parents, 2006-2007 (Folder 9)
  - Summer mailing to parents, 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 1)